{
    "id": "8557916306384b53b0a487a2f32fea91",
    "title": "Both, Either And Neither",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………….. my sisters live in the US.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7c2f806f41e74b22a78810be98b025f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. of them were ill and didn’t go to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "64cd01407fdc4b8d836ddc7295738463"
        },
        {
            "question": "I know you don’t like me. I don’t like you ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "47132f425d8a4358b5c526d15be356c6"
        },
        {
            "question": "John didn’t come. …………….. did Peter.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "885714e15b174713943001f483f4987b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t like ………………… of these colors.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7ddea960d7cb43c8a5bd221fb5c00280"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can’t decide between these two dresses. I like them …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef774b52aa8b4ba2ac780b07cdbbf086"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………… cheese or butter will do.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Either",
                "Neither",
                "Both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bb5a6ea136724b59a29a9bbbec278196"
        },
        {
            "question": "We can ……………….. swim.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c1466934161e429d89d4b9c4bdb7914f"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. of them is here.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "db215861225a499fb69943e74d5512b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t like ……………….. of them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "neither",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9fa3e0a1f75c47c192f9c98bcb09c1d6"
        }
    ]
}